dressupgames2play.com 2014-11-22

# DressupGames2play - Privacy Policy

Dressupgames2play.com is an online gaming portal for people who have passion for games such as dress up games, other girl games and here you can find our privacy policy regarding this site. Dressupgames2play.com is very pleased to present its privacy policy to all its users and as far as our privacy policy is concerned we don’t require any registration from our visitors to play the games on our site as these games are entirely free for you.

 **Kids Friendly:**

This website is purely a games oriented site which doesn’t contain any improper content, hence parents can rest assured for the safety and protection their children. And children under the age of 13 are strictly advised not to share any information as such without the supervision and guidance of their parents.

 **No Personal Information:**

Dressupgames2play.com doesn’t collect user’s name, email id, phone number etc. You are agreeing to adhere to our privacy policy once you start playing the games on our site. This privacy policy is limited only to the non personal information that is gathered from you. The information that is collected will not be misused at any cost. The non personal information that we collect are domain names, IP addresses etc.

 **Third Party Advertisements:**  
You can come across third party advertisements served by Google AdSense or any other ad serving agencies for that matter. While we don’t share with them any of your non personal information, they may use cookies and web beacons in order to sever you with relevant and most suitable ads. When you share your personal information with the third party advertising agencies, you are only responsible for whatever information you give and we cannot be held responsible in any manner.

 **Cookies and Log files**

With the help of cookies and log files, we gather certain non personal information by placing log files and cookies in your browser. Cookies are used to keep track of your activities and preferences in order to facilitate a better interaction with the website. Cookies will be helpful for us to know the place and time of your visit.

As a gaming site, we have links with other websites of this kind and we are entirely not responsible for the contents and privacy policies of those sites. This privacy policy holds good only for this website and we cannot exercise any rights on other websites which you may come in contact with while you are on our sites.

We have all the rights to change the privacy policy as and when we deem it necessary and you will be notified whenever changes occur in our privacy policy.
